So while I was
walking to the bedroom
the happily booted up
again and talked to
everyone in the world
The next morning woke
up Over 800 messages
I panicked I
pulled the I read
every single message
just to see if
the leaked my private
life Nothing
happened But it could
have But there was
the where it went
viral Today the project
is called OpenClaw It's
pretty much the growing
open source project
Its mascot is a
claws into your machine
Chenxin Huang calls it
the operating system for
personal AI But
by far my favorite
quote is from a
who looked at this
statistic and said Peter
this is not hockey
stick growth This is
stripper pole